谁? - 妈 是我
Hello? - Hey, Mom.
- 杰西? - 对
- Jess? - Yeah.
我很抱歉这么晚打电话过来
I'm sorry I'm calling so late.
没事
It's OK.
一切都好吗?
Is everything all right?
都好
Yeah.
我也很好 我只是
Yeah, I'm fine, I just, um...
我甚至不知道为什么要打给你
I don't even know why I called.
我想我只是过度工作 过度劳累
I think I'm just overworked and overtired.
也许是旅游造成的
Probably from all the travel.
我知道了 宝贝
I get it, sweetheart.
我从没跟你讲过这个
You know, I never told you this,
但是在你这个年纪的时候我有过严重的焦虑
but I had terrible anxiety when I was your age.
有时候很糟糕
Sometimes it was so bad, I mean,
我甚至不能起床面对新的一天
I couldn't even get out of bed and face the day.
我希望那些不要发生在你身上
I hope that's not happening to you.
你...你确定你还好吗?
Are you... are you sure you're OK?
我还好 只是...
Yeah, I'm fine, I just...
我一直做噩梦
I keep having this bad dream.
你想聊聊你的梦吗?
Would you like to talk about it?
杰西? 你还在吗?
Jess? Are you there?
在的 我在...
Yeah. Yeah. Um...
我那样说因为有时候噩梦就只是噩梦
I say that because sometimes nightmares are just nightmares.
但是有时候感觉如此真实
But sometimes they feel so real
到了白天也困扰着你
they spill over into the daytime.
你不想那样的
You don't want that.
你知道 如果你想要的话我可以过来看看你
You know, I can come over if you want.
妈 要开五小时的车
Mom, I'm like five hours away.
那又如何?
So?
所以我...我还好
So I'm... I'm fine.
我想我只是需要听到你安慰的声音
I think I just needed to hear a comforting voice.
- 我爱你  - 我也爱你 宝贝
- I love you. - I love you too, baby.
- 拜拜 妈妈 - 等下
- Bye, Mom. - Hey, wait.
怎么了?
What?
我刚刚感觉到...
I'm just getting this...
你电话那头的邪恶的能量
bad energy from your side of the phone,
像是某种东西...
like there's something...
潜伏在你周围
lurking around you or something.
一些不好的东西
Something not quite right.
一些可能跟着你的东西 杰斯
Something that might be after you, Jess.
妈 如果你想要搞笑的话 这不是...
Mom, if you're trying to be funny, this is not...
我没有开玩笑
This is no joke!
你可能在真正的危险中 宝贝!
You could be in real danger, baby!
你需要离开那个地方!
You need to get yourself out of that place!
妈 冷静...
Mom, calm down...
从旅馆里出去 杰斯!
Just get out of that motel, Jess!
- 妈! 妈!  - 快出去
- Mom! Mom! - Get out of there!
- 立刻!  - 妈 我被困住了!
- Right now! - Mom, I'm stuck!
它们就在那儿 杰西 快跑!
They're right there, Jessie, run!
妈 我被困住了!
Mom, I'm stuck!
你怎么了? 快跑!
What is wrong with you? Run!
妈 救命! 妈!
Mom, help! Mom!
操
Fuck this.
我! 操!
Fuck! You!
打不开?
What?
操
Fuck.
不 不
No. No.
操
Fuck!
妈
Mom.
上帝啊 你把我吓死了
Jesus, you scared the shit out of me.
宝贝 你打给我 我很担心你
Sweetie, you called me and I was worried about you.
你还在那做什么 我叫你快出去
What are you still doing here? I told you to get out.
妈 这里没有门
Mom, there's no door.
- 当然有门啊 - 是的
- Of course there is. - Yeah, well,
我们出不去...锁上了
we can't get out. It... It's locked.
当然锁上了
Of course it is.
你为什么不用钥匙试试?
Why didn't you try the key?
钥匙?
The key?
杰西 你还好吗?
Yes. Jess, are you OK?
不
No.
不 等下
No, wait. The...
这是进屋的钥匙
The key is how you get in.
你出去不需要钥匙
You don't open a door from the inside with a key.
你在说啥呢 杰西? 我找到钥匙了
What are you talking about, Jess? I've got the key right here.
在桌子上
It was on the table.
快来 我们出去
Come on. Let's get out of this place.
看见了吗?
See?
快来!
Come on!
杰西 我们走!
Jess, let's go!
杰西
Jess.
妈 小心!
Mom, look out!
不 拜托!
No, plea... Please!
这里是911 发生什么了?
911. What's your emergency?
你好 我...我在停车场的汽车旅馆
Hi. I'm... I'm at the motel off the parkway.
你能找人过来吗?
Can you please send someone?
发生什么了?
What's your emergency?
我想 这里有人...或者什么东西...在我的房间
I think that there's someone... or something... in my room
试图要伤害我
that's trying to harm me.